I saw a grandfather like that, he had a kitili, well,
я видел деда такого у него китили ну
this jacket was hanging with awards and he
этот пиджак висел с наградами и он
was lying in the middle of the room, killed,
посреди комнаты лежал убитый
shot Yes, I saw this photo too
застрелянный Да я это фото тоже видел
Can you confirm the authenticity of this photo
Подлинность этого фото можешь
Well, damn,
Ну блин
Eh, oops
Э опа
Hello, I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are
Здравствуйте Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
you from? I'm from Barcelona No, don't tell me where you're from I'm going to make every
откуда ты Я же всё равно для каждого
video anyway, so I'll introduce myself Not everyone
ролика так что представляюсь Не все же
knows you Well, I'm telling you, I'm in
тебя знают Ну тебе говорю я сейчас в
Barcelona, ​​Spain now I've
Барселоне Испании Я твои барселонские
already guessed your Barcelona curtains in all the videos
шторы во всех роликах уже угадал
It's Belgorod because there were explosions on
Это Белгород потому что были бабахи на 9
May 9 You had a flag hanging outside your window Yes, I
мая У тебя там флаг висел за окном Да
somehow guessed I remember We already remember
как-то догадался Я пом Мы уже помним
your hut
твою хату
You've studied everything Yes, yes You go there with a drone
Вы же всё изучили Да да Ходишь дрон туда
Yesterday I talked to someone from Canada,
Вчера я вчера с одним общался из Канады
he said: "We, we know you, we
он говорит: "Мы мы тебя знаем мы тебя
saw you on the bloggers' list of the
видели у блогеров ты в списке находишься
dead You'll be killed immediately when the
мертвецов Тебя сразу умертвят когда
Ukrainian army comes to you in
украинская армия придёт к тебе в
Belgorod, you'll be killed immediately" Here's the question: who
Белгород тебя сразу убьют" Тут вопрос:
needs you
ты кому нужен
No, you see, people like  Canada From
Не ну вот видишь люди как из Канады Из
Canada They know me in Canada, imagine It's
Канады Меня в Канаде знают прикинь
cool
Прикольно
People know me on the street Already in Canada
Меня на улице знают люди Уже в Канаде
or in Belgorod In Belgorod It's cool
или в Белгороде В Белгороде Прикольно
You see how famous I am Good They
Видишь какая слава у меня стала Хорошо
even even take pictures, imagine They
Даже даже даже фотографируют прикинь
go and you know from this and take pictures of me and
Идут вот и знаешь из это и фоткают меня
say: "Glory to Ukraine"
говорят: "Слава Украине"
No, not you, many from Russia watch
Нет не у тебя много из России смотрят
just for fun You have such a
чисто по приколу У ты такой это
humorous political show Everything is
юмористическополитическоческое шоу Всё
correct Many
правильно Меня меня много смотрит
Russian people watch me Some even
российских людей Некоторые даже и
do good things in Russia
хорошие вещи делают в России
Like they put it under the rails there, where
Типа там подложили под рельса да там где
non-specialized ministries are
не профильные министерства этим
doing it We are such petty dirty tricks
занимаются Мы так мелкие пакости
No, that's all, look, your people were removed from Kursk There is
Не ну всё смотри из Курска ваших убрали
no Kursk There were no ours in Kursk
Нету Курского В Курске не было наших Не
No, Kursk Sudzhinsky district Well,
ну Курского Суджинский район Ну из Суджи
we left Sudzha, like, we regrouped,
мы вышли типа сделали перегруппировку
and our troops remain in the Kursk region
она и в Курской области остаются наши
Well,
Ну
imagine And was it worth it to climb there, yes
прикинь А стоило туда залазить да
How many of your people and ours died there Well,
Сколько там погибло людей ваших и наших
yours died more, yes Well,
Ну ваших погибло больше да
ours died there Well, look, the question is for
Ну наших там погиб Ну вопрос смотри для
everyone, for all Russians, like, yes, who
всех для всех россиян типа да которые
start, like, why, like, why did
начинают типа а зачем типа для чего
Ukraine need to climb into the course  Do you
Украине надо было лазить в курс Ты
agree that, uh, Ukraine and Russia are at war,
согласен что э-э Украина и Россия воюют
and that means these clashes would have happened
и значит эти столкновения были бы всё
anyway, either in the Sumy region, or in the
равно Либо в Сумской области либо в
Donetsk region, or in the Zaporizhzhya region, yes. That's
Донецкой области либо в Запорожской да
Ukraine's strategy. Why not
Вот то стратегия Украины Почему бы не
have these clashes on the territory of the
делать эти столкновения на территории
Kursk region, where the
Курской области там где менее укреплены
Russian
российские
zones are less fortified, wait, all the more, all the more,
ээ зоны там подожди тем больше тем более
Russia pulled a huge number of
ээ Россия оттянула огромное количество
troops to the Kursk region in order to
войск на Курскую область для того чтобы
recapture this unfortunate Sudzha.
отбить эту несчастную Суджу Уничтожила
It was completely destroyed. Do you agree that when
её полностью Ты согласен что когда
Ukraine entered Sudzha, it
Украина заходила в Суджу она её
received it intact. The Russian army simply
получила целую Русская армия просто
ran away. A bunch of houses were bombed out and there were
убежала Куча домов была разбомбленных и
photographs. Well, look, we're looking at
были фотографии Ну смотри мы смотрим вот
this Pyaterochka, yes, it was simply intact,
эта пятёрочка да она просто целая была
absolutely intact, in the center of the city. Now,
абсолютно целая в центре города Теперь
when the Russian army sort of liberated
когда русская армия как бы освободила
Sudzha, yes, Pyaterochka was completely destroyed.
Суджу да пятёрочка в хлам уничтожена
Pyaterochka. Pyaterochka is located somewhere in the
Пятёрочка Пятёрочка находится где-то в
center of Sudzha. I understand that it's somewhere in the
центре Суджи я как понимаю там где-то в
lowland. In the lowland, it's located somewhere.
низине в низине она находится где-то А
But the fact is that
вот то что вот
Goncharovka, these are the areas that are closer
Гончаровка вот эти районы которые ближе
to Ukraine, there was a bang from the very beginning, my
к Украине там с самого начала бабахало
dear mother. Yeah.  Well, the main
что мама дорогая Угу Ну там главный
question is that in the Suzhinsky district out of 25,000
вопрос что в Сужинском районе из 25.000
population there were 2,000 left under occupation
населения а в оккупации осталось 2.000
When ours entered they found 550 living people
Когда наши зашли нашли 550 живых человек
where the rest were almost there maybe some
где остальные почти там может часть
some went to the Sumy region some
часть часть в Сумскую область выехала
evacuated some were evacuated somewhere else I
эвакуировалась часть ещё где-то эвакуи
have no idea Well, you know, well they
Понятия не имею Ну знаешь ну кучу кучу
found a bunch of basements with dead
нашли подвалов с убитыми
residents from lying on the streets Maybe I
жителямиз на улицах валялись Возможно Я
saw I even saw a video of how uh
я видел я видел даже видео как ээ э
Banderovites shot a veteran of the Great
бандеровцы расстреляли ветерана Великой
Patriotic War and whether his body
Отечественной войны и ли его труп
No I saw I saw such a grandfather he had a
Не я видел я видел деда такого у него
keel well this jacket was hanging with awards and
кили ну этот пиджак висел с наградами и
he was lying in the middle of the room killed
он посреди комнаты лежал убитый
shot Yes I saw this photo too
застрелянный Да я это фото тоже видел
Can you confirm the authenticity of this photo
Подлинность этого фото можешь
Well, damn And the corpse is already so good
Ну блин Причём труп такой уже хороший
Super super Look I remember it was
Супер супер Смотри я помню это было
about two months ago in short damn somewhere this
месяца короче блин где-то два назад эта
info was being chased yes Can you tell me the
инфа гонялась да Можешь вот сказать
last name, first name, patronymic of this grandfather so that we can
фамилия имя отчество этого деда чтобы мы
verify it I don’t remember but it was
верифицировали его Я не помню но было
written Here Here look The thing is that how the
написано Вот Вот смотри Дело в том что
Russian one works  propaganda It
как работает российская пропаганда Она
throws in a bomb, yes, the Banderites killed the old man, in
делает вброс да бандеровцы убили деда
short, a veteran Hop, and a day later, it
короче ветерана Хоп и через день лет
throws in another bomb about other things What kind of
делает другой вброс по другим штукам Что
veteran is this Where was he killed Who
этот за ветеран Где его убили Да кто
killed him Come on Well, the village was named Come on Come on
убил Давай Ну село было названо Ну давай
What kind of veteran
давай давай Что за ветеран
It's very simple If so much time had
Это ж очень просто Если столько времени
passed, I don't know and the UN
прошло уже бы там не знаю и в ООН
would have been fussing over them and that's it You
носились бы с ними и всё
won't find it now Come on, find it Well,
Сейчас не найдёшь Давай так нади Ну это
I don't know that All of Russia would be buzzing The
я же не знаю Вся бы Россия гудела
Banderites killed a
Бандеровцы убили
veteran in Russia simply Well, that's it, the
ветерана в России просто Ну всё ну
veteran there should have been over 90 years old,
ветерана там больше 90 лет должно было
yeah Well, that is, I think that
быть да Да Ну ну то есть я думаю что
this veteran has already been shown on TV
этого ветерана уже ведь по телевизору
his last name, first name, patronymic, uh, the
показывали его фамилия имя отчество ээ
neighbors talked about him Come on
соседи как про него рассказывали Давай
I'm really interested
Мне интересно действительно
Because that's how your Russian
Потому что так работает ваша российская
propaganda works It piles on The Banderites
пропаганда Она наваливает Бандеровцы
killed the Banderites, the Banderites, everything And all this
убили Бандеровцы бандеровцы всё И всё
without evidence
это без доказательств
No, here's a photo That is, this Yes, I saw a photo Well,
Не ну вот такая фотка То есть это Да
I saw this photo
фотку я видел Так я ж фотку эту видел
It was Russian propaganda that took
Это российская пропаганда сделал да Вот
this photo  where it seems to be lying That
эту фотку где там вроде как лежит То
is, this grandfather is already so good Super Yes
есть это дед уже такой хороший Супер Да
Yes Show Yes That's what it is What kind of grandfather is this Come on What kind of
Да Покажи Да Вот что это Что это за дед
grandfather is this Written I don't know I don't know
Давай Что это за дед Написано Не знаю Я
Well, how the hell is there a super famous,
не знаю Ну как блин есть супер известный
in short, a veteran grandfather and it is unknown what kind of
короче дед ветеран и неизвестно что за
grandfather
дед
But what's the point if a person fought there in
А вот смысл если человек воевал он там в
his time even if so Show show
своё время даже если так Покажи покажи
No let's do it again so that we can, according to the facts,
Нет давай так ещё раз чтобы мы по фактам
now me and Well, at least you at least
вот сейчас меня с Ну вы хотя бы Вы хотя
understand that if Hitler had won Once
бы понимаете что если бы победил Гитлер
again, come on don't run away don't
Ещё раз ещё раз давай не убегай не
run away Come on show now Yes you said
убегай Давай сейчас покажи Да ты сказал
that the Ukrainian army killed the veteran grandfather there,
что украинская армия да там убила деда
in short, yes, there he was lying in the titel That's
ветерана короче да вот он лежал в тителе
all I saw this photo of Russian
всё я эту фотку российских
propagandists and I specifically
пропагандистов видел да и я специально
monitored it but then there were no
мониторил да не было потом никаких
memories what kind of child this surname
воспоминаний что это за дет фамилия
reference and then the transfer where come on
привязка да потом передача где давай уже
2 months have already passed It's not like they
прошло 2 месяца Это не то что день
showed the day Wow come on 2 months have
показали Вау давай 2 месяца
passed Well I don't know I haven't seen such information Yes,
прошло Ну не знаю такой информации не
as if but find the gist No no don't find
Да как бы а суть найди Не не не найди
come on I want his medals, for example,
давай Я хочу вот вот его медали допустим
Ta  medals Look, I can show you whose
Та медали Смотри я могу сейчас показать
medals these are His whose are his
чьи это медали Его это чьи его записа
So yeah Why
Так вот да Зачем
I don't know Well,
Я не знаю Ну
come on Maybe it's a Ukrainian old man from
давай Может это вообще украинский дед из
Kharkov whom these Russians captured,
Харькова которого эти россияне захватили
brought, and killed there Let's figure out what kind of
привезли убили там Давай разберём что
business this is And why kill somewhere from Kharkov Well,
это за дела А зачем где-то из Харькова
I don't know Maybe the Russians
убивать Ну я не знаю Россияне может
did it, they took some old man Look, we see,
сделали взяли какого-то деда Смотри мы
look what we see We see a
видим смотри что мы видим Мы видим
photograph in which some old man is lying
фотография на которой какой-то дед лежит
dead We see a separate list of his
мёртвый Видим отдельный список его
awards So the question is, what kind of old man
наград Так вопрос что за дед
I don't know I wasn't interested Well, come on I
Я не знаю Я не интересовался Ну давай Я
want to figure it out Let's figure it out
хочу разобраться Давай мы разберёмся
now You really raised this
сейчас Действительно ты ж поднял эту
topic, right That is, you are
тему да То есть ты несёшь
responsible for what you say Well,
ответственность за то что ты озвучиваешь
let's figure out what kind of girl this is where No, no, it's not hanging No, no, it's not
Ну давай разберём что это за деви куда
hanging
развисни
And hang it up, hang it up We have to find the old man Well, hang it up
А развесни развисни Мы же должны найти
We want to find the old man
Ну развисни Мы хотим найти деда
This is the old man
Это
Or maybe it was the old man from Belgorod who was
дед А может это белгородского деда там
killed there Everything seems to be That's how the
убили Всё походу Вот так работает
Russian system works  propaganda Yes, they pile up
российская пропаганда Да они наваливают
a photo, a story, anything, yes And every
фотографию там историю что угодно да И
other day it is
она через день она эмоционально
perceived emotionally: "All Banderovites killed a
воспринимается: "Всё бандеровцы убили
veteran" And every other day they forget about it
ветерана" А через день о ней забывают
because they pile up some new
потому что наваливают какую-то новую
news Yes And they already forget about that one Nobody
новость Да И за ту уже забывает Её никто
checks it That's all Where is the grandfather 2 months have
не проверяет Вот и всё Где дед 2 месяца
passed What kind of grandfather Already the
прошло Что за дед Уже аж приехал бы
first TV channel would have come and filmed a video about him Where is the
первый телеканал снял бы видос о нём Где
grandfather Well,
дед
hello So we then You zaviz on what
Ну привет Так мы тогда Ты завиз на чём
On Sudzhi
На Суджи
Nenene Something you were looking for
Ненене Что-то ты искал
Grandfather We were looking for you and me Yes, yes, yes Killed Yes, the
Деда искали мы с тобой Дадада Убит Да
murdered grandfather, in short, by Banderovites,
убитого деда короче бандеровцами
crucified there, murdered Found
распятого там убитого Нашёл
I found that his son's name is Nikolai
Я нашёл что его сына зовут Николай
Nikolaevich and they gave him awards and
Николаевич и ему передали награды и гроб
made a coffin Super Super That's why they didn't
сделал Супер Супер То де фамилию не
indicate the last name And is there some on official
указали А есть какой-то на официальных
resources Well, there, uh, the prosecutor's office, the
ресурсах Ну там вот ээ прокуратура
police, that grandfather is such and such I understand I understand
полиция что вотвот дед такой-то такой-то
In short, we cannot
Понял Понял Короче мы не можем
identify this grandfather No, I
идентифицировать этого деда Да не я тебе
can't show you the video Another woman
могу показать видео Женщина другая
was telling
рассказывала
how they killed her son That's it, watch
как убили убили сына её Всё смотри
Woman, let's go  with grandpa first they burned down the
Женщина давай мы с дедом сначала раз
house Let's deal with grandpa first
сожгли сожгли дом Давай мы сначала с
And did you see the video in
разберёмся А ты видел короче видео в
Suzha, in short, this guy who first
Суже этот мужик который сначала
told the Ukrainians, damn, how it is here Yes, in
украинцам рассказывал блин как тут Да вы
short, you are great, we are all here, yes, thank you for
короче молодцы мы тут всё да спасибо за
this And then he told your governor, not
это А потом вашему этому губернатору не
yours, but Kursk's Khinshtein:
вашему а курскому Хийнштейну рассказал:
"Damn, it was so hard for us here, they
"Блин нам тут так тяжело было нас тут
mocked us so much" Saw Not Okay I'm coming to you,
так издевались" Видел Не О'кей Я к тебе
prima Didn't see No, I didn't see I saw No,
примам Не видел Нет не видел Видел я Нет
I'm telling you this guy who says the
я тебе говорю этот мужик который одно и
same thing, therefore, what the granny
то же говорю поэтому то что там бабка
will tell on camera and what she will tell her what
расскажет на камеру и что ей скажет то
she will be told Say Okay And I will
что ей скажут Сказать О'кей И я буду
tell you how good you are if you
говорить вам какие вы хорошие если вы ко
come to my house with a machine gun Of
мне придёте домой с автоматом Тож
course too That's why I'm telling you that the granny to
конечно Поэтому я тебе говорю что бабка
whom Russian troops came with a
которой пришли российские войска с
machine gun will say anything so that the FSB
автоматом да скажет что угодно чтобы ФСБ
doesn't take her to the basement
не взяла на подвал
Well, I don't think they need them Well,
её Ну я не думаю что они им нужны Ну
1,000 people have disappeared More than a thousand
1.000 человек пропало Больше тысячи
Maybe no one knows where they are Well, the
Возможно никто не знает где они Да ну
Russian army was shelling Suzha,
российская армия ж обстреливала Судже
bombing
бомбардировала
And you  bombed No So wait Ukraine
И вы бомбили Нет Так подожди Украина
came Sudzha Didn't bomb Inna came Sudzha
пришла Суджу Не бомбила Вна зашла суджа
was whole they brought in different international
была целая привозили международных
journalists
журналистов
Well and the point of this was the
разных Ну а смысл вот этого было
attack on Sudzha what did it give you It
наступление на Суджу что оно вам дало
was just interesting We have
Просто интересно было
n't been to Sudzha yes Well you know there's Kursk
В суджи не были да Ну знаешь там Курская
region these towns they don't have anything
область вот эти городки они ничего
interesting there Well we went in and looked
интересного там нет Ну зашли посмотрели
nothing interesting came out I mean
ничего интересного вышло
when I lived in Kursk region for a year and a half
Я вот я когда полтора года жил в Курской
in a similar town like Sudzha
области вот в похожем городке типа Суджи
I gained 15
я набрал 15
kg There the main entertainment was to fill your
кг Там главное развлечение было набить
belly after work
себе брюхо после работы
in the evening you can't go out or take a walk Well there
вечером Там не сходить не погулять
was a swimming pool Well look but how it came
Ну бассейн был Ну смотри зато как пришла
how they came from DSU there was so much entertainment for the
как пришли из ДСУ столько развлечений у
locals yes they run around the
местных жителей стало да бегают по
basement and hide from Russian cabs
подвалу и прячутся от российских кабов
So like it's really cool
Так типа вообще круто
Well I don't think they really hammered the elderly area Well
Ну не думаю что прямо пожилым районом
you've seen the photos of the
долбали Ну ну ты видел фотографии
destroyed Sudzha I saw There's some left
разрушенной суджи Я видел Там осталось
Well I came and said: "We will restore
так приехал сказал: "Мы восстановим
Sudzha" I'm like: "Uncle, I
Суджу" Я такой: "Дядя
don't know here within a radius of 20 km from the
ты тут не знаю в радиусе 20 км от
border there shouldn't be a single resident
границы вообще ни одного жителя не
Look it turns out you  I saw what the
Смотри получается ты видел что
Russian army did to it right there,
российская армия сделала с тут жей так
it was simply
она просто
destroyed. And now you're asking where they were
уничтожена А теперь ты пытаешь куда ж
asking where the people disappeared to.
спрашивают куда ж пропали люди
You took them away to your place. Or maybe you didn't
Да вы их утащили к себе А может и не
take them away.
утащили
Well, the FSB was spreading the news that
Ну ФСБ распространяла новость что
Ukraine was massively evacuating residents of Sudzha and the
Украина массово вывозит жителей Суджи и
region in special camps. Well, what
района специальные лагеря Не ну то что
Ukraine was
Украина
doing was
проводила то то что Украина проводила
evacuating your Moskalkova or
эвакуацию ваша ж Москалькова или
Moskaleva as the
Москалёва как за уполномоченная по
Human Rights Commissioner. She also said that the Armed Forces of Ukraine
правам человека она же говорила что ЗСУ
was evacuating women, children, and so
проводила эвакуацию женщин детей и так
on, and so on, on the territory of the Sumy region.
дальше да на территории Сумской области
Then they were given access
Потом им давали выход на это
to Kursk or wherever, or to
на Курскую или куда там или на
Belgorod. Well, they exchanged and
Белгородскую Что ж обменивались они
launched. She said that,
запускали Она говорила что вот как раз
like, thank you for doing this with the copper
типа спасибо что так делали с медными
residents, for helping them evacuate.
жителями что помогли им эвакуироваться
Very clearly. They brought a pregnant woman to the
Чётко очень Там беременную э женщину в
maternity hospital in Sumy, and she
Сумы в роддом завезли было она там
gave birth there. Well, there is a need here,
родила Ну здесь необходимость здесь
naturally. I don't know. There is a
естественно Я А не знаю тут же есть
maternity hospital right there. So maybe there is a maternity hospital, but there might
роддом Так роддом- то может и есть а
not have been any doctors.
врачей-то могло не
What is this? So, look at the question.
быть Что ж такое Так вопрос смотри
It turns out that Russia bombed Sudzha knowing that there were
Получается Россия бомбила Суджу зная что
so many there.  civilians left Yes, I don't
там столько мирного населения осталось
know No, they climbed through the pipe
Да не знаю Не ну они же через трубу
poured positions to win the Kabami Well, you
наливали позиции побе кабами Ну ты же
bombed Sudzha with FABs, Kabami and these ones Uh, it was bombed
фабами кабами да вот этими Ээ бомбили
It was
суджу Она
simply torn to pieces All the
просто на шмате разорвана Разораны все
houses were torn apart Well, what Well, you went to Krasnaya
дома Ну что Ну вот вы сейчас на Красную
Ruga now, no Well, wait, look, the
Ругу пошли не Ну подожди смотри ты вот
community center was like this and it
дом культуры вот такой был и вот такой
became like this No Yes and won't be And in Mariupol, the
стал Нету Да и не будет А в Мариуполе
community center was
дом культуры был
with people with children and an aerial bomb was dropped on
с людьми с детьми и авиабомбу скинули на
it So our people say that yours
него Так наши говорят что это ваши
dropped it specifically so that Yes And our people
скинули специально чтобы Да А наши
dropped it How could our people drop an aerial bomb
скинули Как наши могли скинуть авиабомбу
if our people weren't flying there They
если наши там не летали
flew Like our people flew There was a
Летали Как летали наши В окружении были
contingent in the encirclement, they found it surrounded No, there was a
контингент на застали был в окружении Не
bomb there, but something else Who am
ну там ушнявая бомба а что-то другое Кто
I not understanding, what could some kind of missile have
я не разбираюсь что может ракета
flown What kind of missile
какая-то полетела Какая ракета
What power
Какой мощности
Big
Большой
Yeah Oh, I found your constitution, it's cool They are
Угу О я нашёл вашу конституцию классную
distributing the Ukrainian constitution on our Internet,
У нас в интернете распространяют
like it was adopted on January 23, 2023
типа была принята 23 января 2023
and  there it says that the state
года и там написано что государственными
languages ​​are Ukrainian and
языками является украинский и
Russian I started reading I read in all
русский Ячала читаю читаю на полном
seriousness that the Constitution of Ukraine damn
серьёзе что Конституция Украины блин
when I start reading I come across this article
когда я начитаю натыкаюсь на эту статью
I just laugh I think damn well
я просто ржу думаю блин
some kind of fake constitution of Ukraine
ну какая-то фейковая конституция Украина
where it says that the Russian language
где написано что русский язык
has state status The
государственный статус имеет
Constitution of Ukraine needs to be read on the
Конституцию Украины нужно читать на
website of the Verkhovna Rada Zelensky as
сайте Верховной Рады Зеленскому как
soon as as soon as it began Once again
только как только начиналось Ещё раз
look Russian Belarusian is
смотри русский белорусский уже это
no longer interesting to anyone Constitutions
никому не интересно Конституции
fictions yes We now just what are we
фикституции да Мы теперь просто что
doing We have them by the way from there you
делаем Мы у них кстати оттуда же ты
say why like entered
говоришь зачем типа входили Номерок
Cool number to get from there Look Oh Oh
классный достать оттуда Смотри Ой Ой Ещё
By the way there is also a sign for Belgorod from Kursk
кстати есть знак на Белгород из Курской
region Nak Belgorod we had on the fund
области Нак Белгород у нас на фонде было
Even this Belgorod so it will not
Даже это такому Белгороду так это не
calm down Unpacking Well because with
успокоиться Распаковка Ну потому что с
Belgo Belgorod was like one of the
Белго Белгород как бы был одним из
first who took the blow of the
первых да кто принял на себя удар
SVO And now somehow to Belgorod well
СВО А сейчас уже как-то к Белгороду ну
everyone there after the Kursk region is calm about
все там после Курской области спокойно
this People are very calm in Belgorod
этому Люди очень спокойные в Белгороде
What-what People are calm about this already
Что-что Люди спокойно к этому уже
Well yes in Kursk they were also
относятся Ну да в Курске тоже относились
calm for now  didn't run
спокойно пока не попёрли
away from Sudzha
убегать из суджи
Well by the way cool
Ну кстати классная фотография
historical photo Blgorod Ukrainians
историческая Блгородские украинцы
city Beruch Germans came they see they are
город Берюч Пришли немцы они видишь они
bosses And they have Mausers in their hands They were given
боссы И у них маузеры в руках Им дали
this they ran And here he is a Hungarian standing
они это побежали А вот он венгр стоит
Hungarian soldier And what occupation Well you
венгерский солдат И что оккупационный Ну
see they ran they were hiding somewhere when the
видишь побежали они где-то прятались как
Germans came they took machine guns these
пришли немцы они взяли автоматы эти
rifles these that they were given and bosses Bosses It's
ружья эти что им дали и боссы
strange to see a person with a
Боссы Странно видеть человека с
machine gun and a boss Bosses bosses If you
автоматом и и боссом Боссы боссы Если
look at uh in the central black earth there were a
посмотришь на ээ в центральном чернозёме
lot of people walking around as bosses And they
очень много люди ходили боссами Причём
were in good beautiful
были в хорошей красивой в красивой
clothes yes but bosses were such a fashion You see
одежде да но боссы была такая мода Видиш
he has a green embroidered shirt And what
вышиванка у него зелёная И что
What do you want to say to all of this Are you
Что ты хочешь этим всем сказать Злые вы
some kind of evil No we are kind No and then would have And
какие-то Нет мы добрые Не а потом бы А
then well they would have won
потом бы вот ну победил победили бы они
and then would have them wow They would You would not
бы а потом бы их бы вауш Они бы Вы бы
care at all Look this was they
вообще всё равно Смотри это было они
were citizens of What Were citizens of the
были гражданами Чего Были граждане
Soviet Union and residents of the RSFSR yes
Советского Союза да и жителями РСФСР да
Because  you in the RSFSR are all traitors
Потому что вы в РСФСР все предатели
You are the Vlasovites Well yes
Вот это вы власовцы Ну да
Why do you say that it is Ukrainian Yes it is
Почему ты говоришь что это украинец Да
Russian from Belgorod It is the city of Beruch There is a
это русский из Белгород Это город Берюч
city of Beruch
Город Берюч такой есть
82% Stop stop What republic was it
82% Стоп стоп Какая это республика была
It was the Belgorod region Well now the
Это была Белгородская область Ну сейчас
RSFSR yes Russian Soviet
РСФСР да Российская Советская
Federative Socialist Republic
Федеративно-социалистическая Республика
Traitors Yes You are Russian traitors
Предатели Да Вы предатели российские
K these are Ukrainians Vysheva No don't wait So
К это украинцы Вышева Нет не подожди Так
when you need it it is Russians when you don't
вам когда нужно это русские когда не
need it it is Ukrainians No it is the RFSR RSFSR
нужно это украинцы Нет это РФСР РСФСР
now they don't tell you that it is
теперь не рассказывают что это
Ukrainians I don't understand what you want to
украинцы Я не понимаю что ты вот хочешь
say with this Look now your country is being
этим сказать Смотри сейчас твою страну
destroyed eh your country is being destroyed yes
уничтожают э твою страну уничтожают да
NATO missiles are ironing Kursk
натовскими ракетами утюжат Курскую
region your Belgorod And you something
область твою Белгородскую А ты что-то
about the Constitution of Ukraine about some
про Конституцию Украины про какие-то
photos from the forty-fifth year
фотки сорок пятого года
No one is being destroyed there everything is calm It is
Никто не уничтожается там всё спокойно
inconvenient to watch TV there when this
Там телек неудобно смотреть когда эта
air raid alarm is announced
воздушная тревога объявляется через
every 30
каждые 30
minutes Well you already know everyone is walking around
минут Ну уже уже знаешь уже ходит всем
there the siren is screaming everyone is going about their
по там сирена кричит все ходят по своим
[music]
[музыка]
business What is
делам Что
there to cry about or
там плакать что
what  They iron harder, you know In the
ли Сильнее утюжат понимаете В
Belgorod region, I see in the
Белгородской области я смотрю в
Belgorod region, the Russian army
Белгородской области российская армия
blew up a dam with an aerial bomb Yes, so that
подорвала с авиабомбой дамбу Да чтобы Да
Ukraine would advance more slowly toward Popovka
Украина медленнее к Поповке продвигалась
or wherever Well, what did they take away this Kamenka
или куда там Ну они что это Каменку эту
Kamenskoye And it turns out that
забрали Каменское И то получается
Ukraine has now liberated a couple of villages in the
Украина сейчас освободила пару сёл
Belgorod region Yes, yes, there are
Белгородской области Да да там сёл уже
no villages left there What villages Places Well, there was
не осталось Какие сёла Места
some kind of lake There were many
Ну там какое-то озеро было Там много
lakes
озёр
blocked off I already
перекрытых Я уже оттуда
left there and sold all the real estate I
уехал продал недвижимость всё что было В
mean And you're not sitting in Belgorod now
смысле А ты не в Белгороде сидишь сейчас
No, somewhere in Voronezh I wo
Нет в Воронежской где-то
n't tell you Why I
Я тебе не скажу Зачем
understand You said that they would recognize you there in
Понял Вот ты говорил что тебя там в
Belgorod
Белгороде узнают
And there and where I live A
Да и там и где живу
man sits on a bus and starts
Мужик сидит в автобусе давай меня
taking pictures of me And laughs I say: "Why have
фотографировать И смеётся Говорю: "Что
n't you seen me
ты меня не видел что
?" You see And where does he see you It's not
ли?" Видишь А он тебя где видит Не
just that all this is sad All this is sad
просто всё это печально Всё это печально
We will not have a future You will not have a
У нас не будет будущего У вас не будет
future normally And why are you so
будущего нормально А что вы так
sad that you will not have a future
запечалили что у вас не будет будущего
Well, because everything will be like this
Ну потому что всё будет
Wait And for you and for you  we don't have what
так подожди И у вас и у нас нет то что у
we have is clear because you attacked us
нас понятно потому что вы на нас напали
you are breaking up our country here And it
вы нам страну тут разбиваете А
turns out that America is your ally No
получается что Америка вам союзница Нет
wait wait Look for for you for
подожди подожди Смотри для для вас для
you so you started your you were telling
вас так вот вы начали свой рассказывали
me here all the Russians were telling me everything
мне тут все русские рассказывали всё у
we have new territories new people Listen and
нас новые территории новые люди Слушай а
now do you understand that everything is
теперь вы понимаете что у вас всё
not okay with you yet And for now it's okay And
не всё нормально пока А пока нормально А
when will it be So far everything is okay while
когда будет Пока пока всё нормально пока
salaries are growing pensions are indexed there
зарплаты растут там пенсии индексируют
Since April 1 they raised pensions by
Вот с 1 апреля подняли пенсию на
8% for people That is somehow everything is
8% людям То есть как-то всё
moving Well everyone understands it will pass there but
движется Ну все понимают там пройдёт но
this, you understand, is a conflict for 10 years
это понимаешь это конфликт лет на 10
now
теперь
With a perspective of 10 years But Putin will be
С перспективой в 10 лет Но Путину будет
what 83 in 10
сколько 83 через 10
years Yours will not live to see the bird
лет Ваш не доживёт до птися
He does not live long Yeah I get it He constantly
Он не живут долго Угу Понял Он постоянно
scratches himself his nose
себя вот нос себе свой чешет
Well they will make a clone for him because he is
Ну там клона ему сделают потому что он
not the same anymore He already died in
уже не тот Уже тот умер в двадцать
1922 And they put this doll in place
втором году А это куклу поставили
Well his wife is doing well in New York and does
Ну жена его хорошо в Нью-Йорке
not deny herself anything You
поживает ни в чём себя не отказывает Ты
are sleeping with her there in New York In general,
там с ней спишь в Нью-Йорке Да вообще
here I am now  I'm sitting in New York
вот я сейчас у неё в Нью-Йорке сижу
Cool In the dirt room And you were
Прикольно В комнате для грязи А ты
with some girl some time ago
вообще с какой-то девушкой когда-то
Naturally Why did you
Естественно
lower your eyes With this Zelenskaya
А что глаза опустил С это Зеленской
girl Why are you translating the joke What
девушкой А что ты шутку переводишь
Where are you dam What can't I
что А где же ты дамба Что не могу Я тебе
want to show you the dam And I saw the video
хочу показать дамбу А я видел видео
In short, it's coming for you and for us
Короче короче наступает и вам и нам У
You're scared to go out on the street, a
вас страшно выйти на улицу
man, that they'll grab you and drag you away And what's scary for you
мужику что схватят и утащат А у вас что
Well, damn, who knows what will happen Maybe some kind of
Ну блин хва знает что будет Может сейчас
economic collapse will start there now
там экономический коллапс начнётся
And is this stackflation really starting, it's going on, it's going on I do
какой-нибудь А начинается правда эта
n't know, but for now these 21% mortgages How do you
Не знаю но пока эти 21% ипотека Как
feel about the fact that in Moscow, St. Petersburg
относишься к тому что в Москве в Питере
and other cities in Russia, this is what happened on
и в других городах России вот это на
Uraza Bayram, on Quran Bayram, there
ураза Байрам на Куран Байрам такие
were such huge crowds of Muslims Well, what do you
огромные толпы мусульман были Ну как ты
think Don't you think that this is somehow
относишься Не считаешь что это как-то с
becoming more and more widespread every year There are
каждым годом принимают всё больше и
only four mosques in Moscow, and there are at least 3 million of them in
только а их по оценкам не меньше 3 млн в
Moscow And they're going, going, and Central
Москве И они прутся прутся и Средней
Asia
Азии
And what's the population of Moscow in general
А сколько населения Москвы вообще
Officially 13 That is, wait 3  million
Официально 13 То есть подожди 3 млн
Officially all 20 Well, even if
Официально все 20 Ну хорошо даже если
all 20 3 million is every sixth Well,
все 20 3 млн - это каждый шестой Ну
naturally there are a lot of them It turns out that every
естественно их много Получается каждый
sixth is a migrant or just a Muslim Yes Yes
шестой мигрант или просто мусульманин Да
Plus they are united they are
Да Плюс они сплочённые они
organized
организованные
Thanks to theirs we have a lot of people
Благодаря сво у нас много людей
who know how to use
появилось которые умеют пользоваться
weapons So that's a
оружием Так что это
plus if it seems like there is someone to send
плюс если кажется есть кого направить
Oh, and they shot cluster munitions at some helicopter
О ещё по какому-то вертолётному
airfield in the Belgorod region with Hymers
аэродрому в Белгородской области
Where is that I don't know where the
стреляли Где это Я не знаю где
helicopters are We only have two
вертолётные у нас Вот у нас только два
airports in the region And they are so
аэропорта в области И такие они
damaged
повреждены ударные вертолёты
K-52 attack helicopters km from the border
К-52 км от границы
Our Valuyki
Наш Валуйки
Not Valuyki is closer probably
Не Валуйки ближе наверное
We have a businessman in Oskol he has a
У нас в Осколе есть бизнесмен у него
personal
личный
helicopter And he built a house with a
вертолёт И дом построил с вертолётной
helipad on the roof and flew it all the time
площадкой на на крыше и летал постоянно
Now he is selling it for 300 million
Теперь он продаёт за 300 лямов
Listen, have you seen the news that in
Слушай а ты видел новости что в
some regions of Russia they are planning
некоторых областях России ээ планируют
payments if schoolgirls get
выплаты если школьникицы будут
pregnant I saw this,
беременеть видел это
damn, I don't know
блин не знаю
Now I'll just google it Schoolgirls yes
Сейчас прям нагуглю Школьницы да
And who will feed the children Here
А и кто будет детей кормить Вот
schoolgirl I had one girl in my group
школьница У меня вот в группе была одна
she got pregnant in her second year
девушка она на втором курсе забеременела
and gave birth to a child in her third year
а на третьем курсе родила
Even two of them
ребёнка Даже две
And there, in short, well, a small child of
таких И там короче ну маленький ребёнок
classes
занятий
Kuzbass This is the Kemerovo region Yes In
Кузбас Это Кемеровская область Да В
Kuzbass the authorities approved a payment of
Кузбасе власти одобрили выплату в
100,000 rubles to pregnant schoolgirls,
100.000 руб беременным школьницам
college students and full-time university students You
студенткам колледжа и вузы обучающимся
know, let them shove these 100,000
очно Знаешь пусть они эти 100.000
up their ass Now now there
засунут себе в одно место Сейчас сечас
was another region there Tverskaya
ещё какая-то область была там Тверская
or now
или сечас
So so This is Kemerovo yes Similar
Так так Это Кемеровская да Аналогичную
assistance has already been carried out in Karelia Khabarovsk
помощь уже вели в Карелии Хабаровском
Krai Oryol Region and Bryansk
крае Орловской области и Брянской
Regions
областях
That is, it turns out
То есть получается
that the authorities are
что власть
hanging It turns out that the authorities stimulate
завис Получается что власть стимулирует
pregnancy, say, among
беременность скажем среди
minors
несовершеннолетних
No, you most likely don’t understand if an
Нет это скорее всего не понимаешь если
adult man slept with a
мужик взрослый переспал с
minor then this man
несовершеннолетней то этому мужику
faces a
грозит
serious term
срок серьёзный срок
If there are two schoolchildren then
Если там два школьника то
damn I don’t know This is most likely some kind of
блин не знаю Это скорее всего как бы
help You do you understand, don’t you understand
помощь Ты ты же понимае ты же понимаешь
that now this will be used
что что сейчас это будет использовать
just like all sorts  disadvantaged strata of the
как раз всякие неблагополучные слои
population all sorts Damn, well, 100,000 Well, this is
населения всякие Блин ну 100.000 Ну это
not much money for you This is not
ну это небольшие деньги для тебя Это
much, yes And for example, for
небольшие да А например для алкошей
some alcoholics and so on,
каких-то и так дальше
they are not allowed to reproduce at all Well, you
у им вообще нельзя размножаться
see my personal opinion Here they are,
Ну вот видишь моё личное мнение Вот они
damn it, going to
блин такое будут
do this So what And why does this Russia do
делать Так что А зачем делает эта Россия
such nonsense
такую дичь
No, in any case, if this
Не ну во всяком случае если такое
happened, if it is a minor, a minor,
случилось если это малолетная малолетняя
having an abortion, most likely she will
делает аборт скорее всего потом она
not be able to have a child at all
вообще не сможет завести ребёнка
Yeah Well, like a consolation prize, here you go,
Угу Ну типа утешительного приза нате
100,000
100.000
Buy
Купите
diapers with
подгузников
nipples Well, again, damn, are you crazy
сосками Ну снова блин вы что с ума
No, I had two girls
сошли Не ну у меня вот было две девушки
in my third year who gave birth They were both
на третьем курсе родили Их обоих
transferred to the evening department The girl
перевели на вечернее отделение Аккуратша
herself took them by the hand in the fifth year and
сама за ручку их взяла на пятом курсе и
led them away She says: "I myself am a mother of three
и отвела Говорит: "Я сама мать троих
children, I understand how hard it is for you You will
детей я понимаю как вам тяжело Вы за
not graduate from the full-time department
очное отделение не
So that's how it is I
выучитесь Так что
understand Here I also read In the Irkutsk
так-то Понял Тут ещё читаю В Иркутской
region, a strategic bomber
области стратегический бомбардировщик
fell This Ace 22M3 And you are happy Yes,
упал Этот Туз 22М3 А вам радостно Да
happy because yes, it is from these
радостно потому что да это ж с этих
bombers are hitting us and you do
бомбардировщиков лупят по нам а их новые
n't produce new ones Here
у вас не производят Вот эти старые
you see these old ones are all worn out,
видишь всё изно изнашиваются
worn out, falling Super And also a pilot They don't
изнашиваются падают Супер Ещё и пилот Не
produce line equipment No, these
лайну технику производят Нене вот эти
bombers are not strategically
бомбардировщики стратегически не
produced in the modern USSR
производят современно СССР
Well, you'll come up with something now
Ну будешь сейчас что-то придумывать
We do
У нас же
[music]
[музыка]
make MS90 yes I personally, I'm
MS90 делают да Я лично я лично
afraid of the Superjet Okay, let's run on
Суперджета боюсь О'кей давай побегу
What Fly on the Superjet and we'll
дальше Что Полетай на Суперджет а мы
read the news Of course Let's
новости почитаем Конечно
go
Так поехали
Subscribe to my Instagram I don't know
Підпишись на мій Instagram Я не знаю для
why you do this, why else should you
чго це тобі для чого ще тобі там
watch it on Face But for you it's one or
дивитись на Face Але для тебе це оди або
three
три
clicks you support me and I'll say:
клика підтримаєш мене и я буду казати:
"Wow, I have a bunch of followers and I
"Вау в мене там купа фоловерів и в мене
'll be cool,
буде класний
tune in to my Instagram, pop Andrey"
настроись на мій Instagram попик Андрей"
Okay, let's wait for you
Отак Давай я тебя чекаю